That's me. Highest sales in the division.
And then. in the morning.
l'm flying back to Omaha.
- That's great.
- Coming through behind you.
- Everything good out here?
- l'm fine. l'm just starving.
- lt's 10.50.
- Oh. right.
Here you go. Oh. and. darling.
you keep the change.
And this one's for you.
Oh. thank you. but l can't. lt's policy.
# It could be love. love.
love Love. love. love #
# Love. love. love. love. love #
# I think it could.
maybe I hope it is. maybe #
# But if we don't feel it now #
Excuse me. darling.
Hello. beautiful.
Pretty drink for a pretty lady?
Sure.
- Cheers.
# Love. love Love. love #
Oh. now. you are thirsty.
aren't you?
Well. aren't you just the sweetest thing?
Thanks. buddy. Gotta jet.
# Love. love. love. love. love #
ls that so?
# I think it could.
maybe I hope it is. maybe #
# But if we don't feel it now
We never will. baby ##
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Oh. come on. Can't get
rid of me that easily.
Any inside tips?
Hey. where are you heading to?
Any good parties?
Because l got a few hours
that l would love to kill.
Yeah. good luck with that.
You sure are a pretty
little thing. aren't you?
Gross. Back off. or l'll vom.
Whoa. why am l tripping?
What was in that drink?
Oh. just something to make
you a little bit friendlier.
We are friends. aren't we?
Come on. baby. just a little kiss.
Back off. creepo.
You good?
A- okay.
You...
are very naughty.
Left without saying goodbye?
Don't you know when a
girl's playing hard to get?
What do you want?
Just one little kiss.
This is so gonna be viral.
Hey.
What about me?
Okay. let's get you out of here.
You're pretty.
l saw you eat some dude's face.
- lt was amazing.
- That's just terrific.
Let's go. Come on.
l'll take you somewhere safe.
Bye- bye. Mr. Smiley- Face.
Hey. Finally decided to show.
So. what do we got here?
Male. mid- 30s. no lD.
just a room key for the hotel.
Woman found him over an hour ago.
- l'd say that's it for witnesses.
- Any cameras in here?
Busted. Checking on the garage's.
Jesus. What the hell happened to him?
You wanna give us a
little space here. Frank?
Yeah. Frank. Why don't you
go canvass or something?
- You got it.
- Thanks. man.
- Vic's human.
- Yeah. Killer definitely wasn't.
Well. our side?
l hope not.
This is sloppy.
Leaving a feed behind like this.
l don't recognise this kind of kill. You?
No. but it's a good way to die.
Dude died with a smile on his face.
Hair.
Brunette.
Got it.
What you got?
He's been drinking.
and l smell a human on him.
Female.
Well. this time of night. that combo.
my money's on the hotel bar.
Sounds like a guy that was here.
But it's been a crazy- busy night.
l can't remember them all.
- Liked the ladies. though.
- How's that?
Kept hitting on our bartender all night.
Leaves. sniffing after some blond.
This bartender. is she a brunette.
by any chance?
Yeah. Name's Bo. She just started
like a week ago. you know.
She's smoking hot.
- So you got a last name? Address?
- No. no.
She's daily. Or was. you know.
She leaves on a bathroom break.
don't ever come back. Totally fired now.
Rush the security tape from
the garage. our eyes only.
- l wanna get a look at this Bo.
- Gotcha.
# Hot sweat Got debt #
# Kept lookin' in the locker
'Cause you don't know yet #
# But I know what I am They
know what they are #
# So let them be #
# Shipshape Ticker tape #
# Looks to me Like a narrow escape #
# But I know what I am They
know what they are #
# So let me be #
# But it's all right It's okay #
# I got the time But the time don't pay #
# I know what I am They know what they are #
# So let me be ##
Nice place while it lasted.
Shit.
Sorry. l was just leaving.
- Where am l? Who are you?
- Just calm down.
You're okay. You passed out.
Would've dropped you home.
None of these wallets appear to be yours.
Nice sideline you got.
- l'm a collector of rare wallets.
- l'm not judging.
- l'm glad you're okay.
- l don't feel okay.
What happened? Did
somebody slip me something?
Some creep in the bar spiked your drink.
You hallucinated a lot
of weird stuff. l bet.
So you didn't- - ? You didn't eat
some dude's face in an elevator?
No. there was no eating of faces.
- Wow. that's crazy.
- Thank God.
That was some crazy- ass shit.
Oh. you kids and your camera phones.
- Don't freak out.
- l'm freaking out.
- What did l just say?
- How can l not? Have you seen you?
- Yes.
- Did you kill him?
- Just slow down.
- Oh. my God. Are you gonna kill me?
You know. that is just stupid.
Why would l save you- - ?
- Are you okay?
- l don't know.
Can you get asthma? l think l'm
totally getting asthma here.
Just breathe.
Fine. l don't need this.
l have to blow town now
after saving your ass...
and find somewhere else to live. again.
You're welcome. by the way.
Excuse me. lady.
- Person.
- lt's Bo.
Hi. Kenzi.
Look. l'm sorry. You- -
You're obviously very
nice for whatever you are.
But l just had. like. the scariest.
weirdest night of my life. okay?
So can we just please talk
about this like normal people?
l think it's fairly clear
that l'm not normal.
Good. Good. Because normal
people do not help out strangers.
lf you were normal.
l could be dead.
l won't tell anyone. Please.
l totally promise.
okay? Just give me like 20 minutes.
Twenty minutes. and you'll never. ever.
ever have to ever see me ever again.
Please?
That depends.
Do you like milk shakes?
Gotcha.
Gotcha. gotcha. gotcha.
Hey. hey. hey. Got it.
- That the bartender?
- Heading to her car with the blond.
Now. look. that's the part l don't get.
Why take the kid?
What. she want a snack for the road? What?
l think she was protecting her.
Hotel put a name to our John Doe.
l pulled his jacket.
He's got a few assaults. He likes
slipping things into girls' drinks.
l'm thinking he targeted the blond.
and the bartender stopped him.
Can you make that plate?
Please.
Good.
Put out an APB. ''Maintain surveillance.
but do not approach.''
- l want us to be first on the scene.
- You got it.
Cheeseburger. onion rings.
# And I'm not done With these
passionate chains #
BLT on brown with fries.
- Are you just gonna stare at me?
- Sorry.
By the way. l know things could've
gotten really messed up for me...
if you hadn't shown up. so thanks.
Oh. well. you're welcome.
- Sunny side up.
- Burger. onion rings.
Okay. Screw it. l gotta know.
Some things are too stupid
to say out loud. so...
Here.
You are a tool. and l don't
know what the hell l am.
Honestly. just a freak. l guess.
- Does it matter?
- Kind of.
l mean. what exactly did you do to him?
lt's hard to explain.
okay? l just- -  l sort of....
- l sort of drain people.
- Oh. my God. Are you a- - ?
Dude. are you a fricking vampire?
No. No. No.
lt's not like that. okay?
lt has nothing to do with blood.
lt's- -  lt's just- -
lt's this hunger that builds and builds...
and then. eventually.
l do what l did last night.
So you can't control it?
- No.
- Wow. that's shitty.
No. l'm serious.
That's. like. no way to live.
You should really work on that.
Thanks.
Are we done with this show-
and- tell? l gotta get going.
- Can l get you anything else?
- No. we're good.
l'm a little short right now.
lf there's any way l can
come back some other time...
and make it up to you...
God.
Yes.
# Swinging from The chains of love ##
Whoa. whoa. whoa. hold up. woman.
What- - ? What the hell was that?
Hey. l'm serious. What was that?
Oh. my God.
How's the tea?
Always the best. Always the best.
You know. when l walked in here.
that waitress...
she was seriously clocking you. man.
- And she looks just like your type.
- l'm sure she does.
Excuse me. l'm gonna
take my game on the road.
- You do that.
- Show you how it's done. baby.
Hello. hello. hello.
- The girl from last night. is it her?
- You tell me.
Female. out- of- towner. unannounced.
Awfully friendly with humans.
lt's beginning. then.
- l can try and stop this.
- How?
l'm not gonna kill her. There are
ways of making someone disappear.
No.
What's meant to be must be.
- We can't fight fate.
- Well. you can.
- What do you want me to do?
- Watch and wait.
l'll help how l can when the time comes.
Hale.
Good job. Okay. we're on our way.
Got a call on the car. Let's shake.
- Let's shake.
- Don't worry about it. lt's on the house.
- Thank you. Keep it warm. please.
- On the house.
You can seduce people into doing
anything just by touching them?
Sort of. lt wears off and takes
a lot out of me. but yeah.
Yet you're broke. live in a crack shack.
and run from town to town.
What are you doing wrong.
girl? That is no life for a sex superhero.
l think l liked you better
when you were scared of me.
No. what you need is some kind of manager.
- l nominate me.
- Shocking. and no. thanks.
Give me a chance. We would make a good team.
Okay. look. this isn't a joke. okay?
Hanging out with a homicidal freak
might not be the brightest move.
Has it occurred to you that l'm
capable of making that decision?
''Homicidal freak.'' God. you are so emo.
- Excuse me?
- Learn to enjoy your shit already.
You can fricking control people by touch...
and not in a creepy hand- job way.
That is awesome.
Fine.
Fine. let's say l take you with me.
What's in it for you?
Out here? Survival.
Mom said. ''Find the toughest
kid on the playground
and make friends with them.''
You are definitely the toughest
kid on this playground.
- lt would kick ass to be your friend.
- l don't know.
Come on. Every superhero needs a partner.
Let me be your Robin.
l'll think about it.
- Take them.
- Here we go.
Kenzi. what's wrong?
- Where are we taking them?
- To The Ash.
- He insists on an audience.
- Sucks to be her.
Guys. seriously. where's my friend. huh?
Where's my friend?
- Just take off the hood.
- Squirmish one. huh?
Oh. you guys have no idea what
you are dealing with here.
Okay. Okay. just take off the hood!
Calm down.
l'm not saying anything without my lawyer.
- Lawyer?
- l know my rights. assholes.
- ls she serious?
- What is this place. huh?
l don't understand your obstinacy.
You know the rules.
Just name your clan.
Buddy. for the last time.
l don't have a clan. okay?
Or bagpipes. or haggis.
l'm not fricking Scottish.
l mean. what the hell kind of
cops are you people. anyway?
- What is this place?
- l'm starting to think she's not faking.
Faking it? Oh. that's great.
So do you truly not know what you are?
What am l?
Forget about me. What the hell are you?
l'm sorry. lt's The Morrigan.
She insists on seeing her.
- You were not invited.
- l know. And l'm hurt.
Cut the shit. Word has it
that somebody's kill...
was improperly dumped in
your territory last night.
And not by a local.
lt'd be nice to know if we
had a new player in town.
We're handling it.
l don't speak to the help.
Hi. Yeah. hello? Could somebody tell
me what the hell is going on here?
Lauren. take her to the lab.
Grab her.
Enough.
Lauren needs to examine the girl.
Please. come with me.
You and l need to talk.
Because l'm your cousin.
and l'm in trouble. you dick.
Yeah. l know your frigging
connections. okay?
You want these wallets?
Trace that plate for me.
Or l'm telling your mom you're being mean.
Asshole.
So. what are you checking me for?
Brands.
Ritual scarring.
The different clans mark
themselves in different ways.
My God. you're beautiful.
l meant that professionally.
lt's cool. l....
l kind of have that effect on people.
Well. that would fit my hypothesis on you.
Would you mind if l asked you some
incredibly personal questions?
Well. all questions feel kind of
personal when you're commando.
Right. Sorry.
Please.
l'll.... l'll answer
yours if you answer mine.
What the hell were those
freaks that l just met?
They're Fae. an evolutionary
branch that predates on humans.
- So am l Fae?
- Yes.
Well. that's your genus. not your species.
And for those of us who flunked biology?
l meant- -
Fae is a general classification.
There are many different types.
So. what type are you?
The ''insatiably curious
human doctor'' type.
- l'm in it for the science.
- Oh. kinky.
Now for the million-
dollar question.
What kind of Fae am l?
The girl doesn't even know she's Fae.
- She's as ignorant as a human.
- And so are you if you believe her.
Oh. come on. l mean. listen to yourself.
You're not seriously suggesting that
she's been hidden from us since birth?
We need to be united in
how we deal with this.
Little problem.
- l'm not a team player.
- lf word gets out we've had a free Fae...
under our noses. we'll be the
laughingstock of the counties.
Let's just kill the bitch.
- lt would be wiser to wait.
- Tell me...
was your neutering
ceremonial or a birth defect?
Her freedom is dangerous to us both.
She cannot be allowed to
exist in between our sides.
Which is why we need to make
her choose between us...
the old way.
l examined your kill
from last night.
Based on your feeding signature. you're- -
Just say it.
- You're a Succubus.
- A Succubus?
Can you fix it?
Well. there's nothing to fix.
You're a perfect biological
specimen of your kind.
Who has a habit of waking
up next to dead lovers.
lf that's not sick.
then l would like a second opinion.
We can help you learn to
control it. if you like.
- That's possible?
- Definitely.
lf you'd been born into a clan.
you would've been taught how.
You'd still have to feed.
but you wouldn't always have to kill.
You deserve a normal life.
and we can offer that to you.
- What's the catch?
- The Fae are divided.
The Light and the Dark. l presume
they'd want you to join one of them...
before they'd allow me
to offer you much help.
l can offer you things.
lf we get out of here.
l know what you're doing.
- Do you want me to stop?
- No.
Didn't think it was gonna
be that easy. did you?
- Girl can dream. can't she?
- Hands. please.
Sorry. Had to try.
No. Good. No. lt was very informative.
- Where are you taking her?
- The glass factory.
- Why?
- lt's neutral territory.
- They're gonna give her the test.
- Without training? That's madness.
lt's not our call.
Did you get it?
Wait. Hold on. hold on. hold on.
Okay. Providence...
Glass lnc. on Front.
Thank you. Owe you one. Bye.
Okay.
Party at the glass factory.
That's not weird.
Pardon the Turkish- prison chic.
lt's a little obvious for my taste.
We can manage chairs. at least.
We're civilised folk.
By the way. congrats on
your amnesia- girl routine.
You've got everybody buying it.
But between you and l. you know
more than you're telling. don't you?
- Do you?
- Okay. Girl's gotta have her mystery.
l can respect that.
l'm sorry. Not to interrupt
your crazy. but who are you?
Local government. Consider me the
welcome wagon for the Dark Fae.
Do you know why you've
been brought here today?
You're gonna be tested.
Will there be math?
Funny. She's funny.
Listen here. Norma Fae...
we have a millennia- old two- party system.
and it works just swell.
Because membership is mandatory.
- l must've lost my invitation.
- Which is a problem.
You see. you running around
free and nonpartisan...
gives all the little
lemmings ideas.
l don't want any trouble. okay? Promise.
Just let me go.
Well. lucky for you.
if you survive your test today...
you'll have the opportunity to
join a side. Problem solved.
Join? Why the hell would l wanna do that?
We take care of our own.
We'll place you in a human
occupation that is to our advantage.
Help with the disposal of your kills.
et cetera. et cetera.
- And dental.
- Well. l'll keep that in mind.
You should.
l hear you've been alone for a long time.
No friends or family.
Afraid you'd kill them. l'd imagine.
Sounds lonely.
You have the chance to be
a part of something now.
Chance to have a new family.
Or to have enemies.
So be very careful how you
play the next few hours.
Welcome to the top of the food chain. doll.
Enjoy it while it lasts.
So. what exactly am l in for here. huh?
Big bad nasties? The Loch Ness Monster?
Under Fae.
- Under what. now?
- Under Fae.
Those of our kind that don't
fit in the human world.
Very old. Very dangerous.
- You'll face two.
- What are my chances?
l wouldn't bet on you.
Have l spit in your coffee?
- What is your deal?
- Kiss me.
Are you bad at reading women.
We don't have time. You need all
of the strength you can get.
- Take some of mine.
- Won't l kill you?
Just kiss me.
Did you- - ? Did you feel that?
That was like- -
That was like the Fourth
of July in my mouth.
Hey. you stopped me.
- No one's stopped me before.
- Fae are different than humans.
Your powers won't work the same on us.
Well. how am l supposed to beat these guys?
You'll be faster.
You'll be smarter.
They're gonna underestimate you.
Use that to your advantage.
l misjudged you.
You got any other advice?
Don't get dead.
And you're back to being
an asshole. That's nice.
Was not expecting Thunderdome.
He's big. but he's slow.
These are your weapons. Choose wisely.
Good luck.
Enough!
To the death.
What are they feeding you down here?
She's probably in there having tea.
Please don't be rats.
Please don't be rats. Please don't be rats.
Gross.
Hello.
- Hi.
- Would you like some tea?
- What just happened?
- l thought we could use some privacy.
Please. sit down.
We don't have much time.
- l want to help you.
- How?
l'm a Pain Eater.
Let me take yours.
l can end your suffering if you'll trust me.
Hello?
Okay.
l'd like to show you something.
Those are your dead.
l don't wanna be here anymore.
l don't wanna see this.
That's all you've been doing.
10 long years.
Killing and running.
Aren't you tired?
Yes.
How many more will have
to die so you can live?
No. No. it's not like that anymore.
l know what l really am.
They told me that l can
learn how to fight it.
You don't actually believe that. do you?
You're an abomination. child.
You know it in your heart.
Do the right thing.
Oh. Bo.
But l don't know what the
right thing is anymore.
Can you help me?
lf you're willing.
What is it?
Your way out.
You'll sleep and never wake up.
- l don't know.
- lt will be quick and beautiful.
A gesture of love.
No one will even miss you.
No one will mourn you.
Nobody needs you.
Bo. wake up!
Bo. wake up. damn it!
Bo. wake up. wake up.
Bo. he's killing you! Wake up!
- Drink.
- Bo!
- Drink!
Bo! Let me go. you big lughead!
Bo!
- Bo. wake up!
- Drink.
No. No.
Get out of my head. you freak.
Help!
She's mine.
This one has passed the test.
lt has been witnessed.
Child. you may name your side.
Neither.
l choose humans.
Now can we kill her?
She passes without any training.
Who is this girl?
May l offer an opinion?
You have no station here. old man.
Don't you have some shoes to
cobble or a garden to decorate?
Someone hid her from both our sides.
lt would be wise to learn why
and who before killing her.
ln the meantime. she could expose us.
Not without exposing herself.
l'm not saying there won't be a
time when she needs to be put down.
l'm saying. choose it wisely.
- Feel like we've been paroled.
- You sort of have been.
Any conditions on our release?
No more evidence for humans to find...
no messing in Fae business.
and no more leaving town.
The elders want you where
they can watch you.
Well. they don't own me.
And l'm not very good at being obedient.
Learn.
- When you need help- -
- lf l need help.
When you need help...
you can find me at the 39th Division.
And. Bo...
you did well.
l knew l smelled po-po.
l'm not crazy.
right? That all just happened?
Yep.
And now we know anyone could be Fae.
My bet's on wiener dude.
So. what now?
We go home. and we figure
out the rest tomorrow.
''We.'' huh?
l gotta figure out some
way to make a living.
And you're the one who thought we'd
be a good team. So. yeah. ''we.''
Cool.
Just so we're clear about
this partnership...
you be you and all. uh.
but l'm only into guys. Sorry.
l'll try to contain
my disappointment.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm